Hello friends welcome back to finance by
bike friends today in this video I am going to
talk to you about s12 company in big s12
april and I am going to give you hight division
and bonus stock is also going to give a good amount
so which is s12 stock how much
dividend will be there exactly what is going to happen I am going to
give you all this information in the video so do watch the video till further notice
and for share market related updates
first of all subscribe to the channel for yourself so
let's
start the video without dairy friends our
first company name is ICC Security
company has announced dividend of ₹95 paisa
ex date is just upcoming
you will get the information on the channel as soon as the update comes let's talk about the
next company banner and hotel company has
made a great announcement of dividend of ₹20
you are also eligible you will get the information on the channel as soon as the update comes let's
talk about the next company
whose industries company
with stock which means so
in day to day stock
company whose name is Master Limited
company has
done ex date record date is just upcoming
update  You will get the information on the channel as soon as it comes. Let's
talk about the next company
in Discover. Gujarat Hotel Company has announced a dividend of ₹2
and the update of this company is also
coming now. You will get it on the channel as soon as it comes. Let's
talk about the next company
whose name is Goyal Aluminum Company has
also bought the stock with 1:10,
which means that the exchange of shares will happen on
25th April, so you can buy the stock till 24th April.
For a good stock bill, let's talk about the next company whose
number is Tata Combination Company has
announced a great dividend of ₹21.
You will get the information on the edit channel, so
subscribe to the channel. In Limited
Exit Record,
Tata Coffee Company has announced a dividend of ₹3.
Exactly what is yours right now,
you will get the information on the channel. Let's talk about the
next company, its name is Ellents
Bank India Company has announced a dividend of ₹5.
Status in seconds, so you
can buy the stock till 24th April.
For a good dividend, let's talk about the
next company.  The company named ICC
Lombard Limited has announced a dividend of Rs 5.50. It is
upcoming now. Let's talk about the next company
named Crystal Limited. The company has
announced a great dividend of Rs 7.
You will get information about all the stocks, so
subscribe to the channel. So friends, if you
like this video, then do like it
and for similar stock market related
information, subscribe to the channel first.